<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Cokt&#039;s Wiki</title>
      <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Cokt&#039;s Wiki</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>The Future</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/The-Future</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/The-Future</guid>
    <description>Cokt awoke in a pile of hay, groggy and sad. As his senses came to, and after internalizing what had just happened, he laid back into the hay and began to sob.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Revolt</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Revolt</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Revolt</guid>
    <description>Krilrym knew that something must be done about the impending doom of his race, so he brought all of the slaves together to formulate a plan. After many nights of late discussion, the Giants and Cokt were prepared to secure their future.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Locht</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Locht</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Locht</guid>
    <description>Locht was the Giant cook on Kovir’s estate. He stayed with the other Giants and prepared their meals after long days of work. Locht would often send Cokt into the kitchen looking for specific ingredients or recipes to add to his repertoire.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Life on the Estate</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Life-on-the-Estate</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Life-on-the-Estate</guid>
    <description>Cokt’s strongest connection was with the Bard, Krilrym. Krilrym acted as the father that Cokt never had. He was a shoulder to cry on and a much needed confidant for a frightened young goblin.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Cokt</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/</guid>
    <description>Cokt is a goblin with a gun. → That’s pretty much it. Table of Contents: Early Life Life on the Estate Revolt .</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Welcome to Quartz</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/index2</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/index2</guid>
    <description>This is a blank Quartz installation. See the documentation for how to get started.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Firearm</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Firearm</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Firearm</guid>
    <description>The Nine Realm’s first firearm was engineered by Kovir the Giant, and commissioned by Rexton Redbrand. It was designed to specifically hunt and destroy Giants, taking advantage of the way they fought and their weaknesses.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Early Life</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Early-Life</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Early-Life</guid>
    <description>Cokt’s earliest memory is behind bars, with the sound of horseshoes and thumping in the background. Falling in and out of sleep and feeling very out of his own control, he remembers being held by enormous hands, strange noises being spoken, and being awoken by a soon familiar face.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Rexton Redbrand</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Characters/Rexton-Redbrand</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Characters/Rexton-Redbrand</guid>
    <description>Rexton Redbrand is a Human hunter, known far and wide for hunting Giants. He travelled around to exotic locations, tracking down and killing the various types of Giants that lived in the area.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Krilrym</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Characters/Krilrym</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Characters/Krilrym</guid>
    <description>Krilrym Quartzheart is a Giant Bard. He grew up with the Dwarves, who raised him and integrated him into their society. He was taken in by a clan of miners, one of which was a Bard himself.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>